tsukamou ze !DRAGON BALL
Let's go grab 'em up! Dragon Ball
sekai de ittou suriru na himitsu
The world's most thrilling secret
sagasou ze !DRAGON BALL
Let's go hunt 'em down! Dragon Ball
sekai de ittou yukai na kiseki
The world's joyful miracle
kono yo wa dekkai takarajima
This whole world's just a giant treasure island
sou sa ima koso adobenchaa !
That's right! Now's the time for adventure!
mune wakuwaku no ai ga GISSIRI
Filled to the brim with heart–pounding love
iro toridori no yume ga DOSSARI
Packed with colorful dreams
kono yo no doko ka de hikatteru
They're out there shining somewhere in this world
soitsu mitsuke ni yukou ze BOY
Let's get up and find 'em, boy
youkaihenge mo buttobashi
Sending all kinds of creatures packing
kumo no mashin de kyou mo tobu no sa
And we'll fly on our cloud machine again today
Let's try try try makafushigi
Let's try, try, try, what a mystery
sora o kakenuke yama o koe
Barreling through the sky, over the mountains
Let's fly fly fly daibouken
Let's fly, fly, fly, a grand adventure
fushigi na tabi ga hajimaru ze
Our mysterious journey is about to begin
te ni irero ! DRAGON BALL
Get 'em in your grasp! Dragon Ball
sekai de ittou tegowai chansu
The world's riskiest opportunity
oikakero ! DRAGON BALL
Go get after 'em! Dragon Ball
sekai de ittou ikashita dorama
The world's most exciting drama
kono yo wa dekkai takarajima
This whole world's just a giant treasure island
sou sa ima koso adobenchaa !
That's right! Now's the time for adventure!
Long, long ago, in a mystery-filled era
none had ever seen or heard of before...
In the deep recesses of the mountains,
cut off entirely from the capital,
there was a lone boy
who lived alongside Mother Nature.
Blooma and Son Gokū
Heya!
Okay! Firewood’s all done!
Boy, I’m hungry...
It should be around here somewhere...
Gramps, I’m headin’ out
to catch some grub.
That’s weird.
I thought I saw ya glowin’...
Gramps!
You do somethin’ just now?
Weird!
Ah, well.
Now, what do I wanna eat?
I had bear the other day...
Yahoo!
Yum!
Feels so good!
I know!
I’m eatin’ fish for lunch!
A monkey!
Time to chow down!
Nothin’ to it!
Big haul, big haul!
Wuzzat sound?
I hit him!
He’s alive!
Mean ol’ monster!
I bet yer after my food, huh?!
You ain’t gettin’ it!
If ya want my food, then bring it on!
Come an’ fight me!
How could you, you monster?!
Huh? A weird yо̄kai’s
comin’ outta the monster!
Jerk!
The heck was that?!
Witchcraft?!
Wh-Wh-What the?!
Wh-Why aren’t you dead?!
Don’t be silly!
I ain’t gonna die that easy!
I trained my body to be
hard like steel!
Yer done for, ya darn yо̄kai!
“Yо̄kai”?!
T-Time out for a sec!
I’m no yо̄kai! I’m human!
Human?
Isn’t that obvious?
Come on, just look at me!
Look!
Don’t move!
Don’t move a muscle!
Are you human?!
Yeah, duh!
You seem kinda different from me...
Ya look all frail and weak...
Well, I am a girl.
A girl? Yer a girl?
You’re a total hick!
You mean you’ve
never seen a girl before?
Nope. I’ve never seen a human
besides me and Gramps before.
Gramps told me that if I ever meet a girl,
I should be real nice to ‘er.
Oh? That’s some fine advice there.
So you live with this Gramps of yours?
He died a long time ago.
Wh-What’s the big idea, handsy?!
So girls don’t got tails?
Huh, that’s funny!
So lame!
Does he think that tail accessory
makes him look cool?
So did this monster catch ya?
This isn’t a monster.
It’s a car.
I heard about ‘em from Gramps,
but this is one of ‘em?
For someone so small,
you sure are strong.
‘Cause Gramps trained me!
Oh, I get it! If you were ridin’ this thing,
does that mean you came from the capital?
Sure does.
Okay, come over to my house!
Yer a girl, so I’ll getcha some food.
Um, w-wait a sec!
It’s further down this road,
so does that mean...
...this kid has it?
If so, then even if he is a little weirdo,
his power should come in handy!
What’s the matter?
Don’tcha wanna eat?
Yep, I’m coming.
I’ll go, but no funny business!
Whaddaya mean, funny business?
You know, funny business is...
Oh, right!
This is his first time seeing a girl,
so he has no idea what that is!
Yer such a weirdo.
Whatever! Follow me!
Oh, by the way,
what’s your name?
I’m Gokū! Son Gokū!
You?
Huh? Oh, um, uh, m-me?
Yeah!
Blooma.
Blooma?
That’s a weird name!
Ugh, and that’s why
I didn’t wanna tell you!
Blooma!
Let it go!
I don’t exactly like it!
This is why I hate kids!
Wait here a sec.
Gramps...
What is it?
G-Gramps is talkin’!
Wasn’t your grandpa supposed to be dead?
There it is!
A Dragon Ball!
Move it!
Hey! Get your hands off Gramps!
“Gramps”? This?
Yup! It’s the only thing o’ his he left me!
Girls ain’t allowed to touch it!
Look, he’s all glowy!
Like he’s excited to talk about somethin’!
Never seen ‘im do that!
Guess I’m gonna have to teach you.
Look!
It’s Gramps!
You got two grampses?!
These aren’t grandpas,
they’re Dragon Balls!
Dragon Balls?
Yeah! Your Dragon Ball is resonating
with the two that I have here.
Try putting yours next to them.
A-All right...
You see?
I found this one in a storeroom
at my house.
I wondered what it was, so I looked into it
and found out that these Balls are incredible!
What’s so incredible about ‘em?
Want me to tell you?
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, there it is!
So this is the legendary Dragon Ball?
So I just chant the words into this?
No.
While that is indeed a Dragon Ball,
it’s useless on its own.
What?!
Pilaf-sama, the Dragon Balls range from the
single-star Yi Xing Qiu to the seven-star Qi Xing Qiu.
Seven of ‘em, eh?
Once all seven Dragon Balls
are brought together...
...Shenlong, known as god of the dragons,
will appear.
If you chant the words then,
he’ll grant you any one wish.
Any wish?
That’s amazing!
I will use the Dragon Balls
to achieve world domination!
So awesome!
So if ya gather all seven Dragon Balls,
any wish’ll come true?
I heard someone became a king
after gathering them all.
But that was a long time ago,
so it seems like they’ve scattered again.
So yer tryin’ to gather ‘em all?
It wasn’t easy, but ten days ago,
I found Wu Xing Qiu here in a valley to the north.
Gramps has got four stars!
That’s Si Xing Qiu!
I already decided on my wish!
It’s hard to give up getting
more strawberries than I could eat,
but I’m set on a cute lover!
So do you mind handing over Si Xing Qiu?
No way, no way, no way!
This’s a keepsake from Gramps!
Oh, come on, you cheapskate!
It’ll be fine!
Not like you’re gonna use it, anyway!
Oh, I get it!
You little devil, you...
What do you say now?
You can touch, but only a little!
I dun wanna touch yer dirty butt.
It is not dirty!
Learn some manners!
Actually, why don’t you
help me look for the Balls?
Your grandpa did tell you
to be nice to girls, didn’t he?
Look for the Balls?
It’s not like you have
anything to do here, right?
If you’re a man, then you gotta
travel around and train up!
If I train,
I can get strong like Gramps?
Of course!
You only know about
these mountains, don’t you?
I bet you’ve never even seen the ocean!
There are towns full of other people,
and you’ll meet dinosaurs and monsters, too!
Sounds fun! I wanna go!
Then it’s decided!
Knew you’d say that!
But I ain’t handin’ this Ball over.
I’ll hold onto it.
Works for me! I’ll just need to
borrow it at the end!
This seems promising!
This kid’ll make the perfect bodyguard,
and so long as I get my wish,
it’s all good!
Let’s go on our fun adventure!
But if we don’t know where the other Balls are,
then how are we gonna find ‘em?
That’s what makes me so smart!
And I got a cute face, too!
Thanks to this!
The Dragon Radar.
I made it myself!
Look! These three dots
are the Balls we have,
and the next is over here.
Um... About 1200 kilometers west!
I dun get it.
Regardless, we can’t just walk there.
Since you totaled my car,
we’ll have to use something else.
Let’s see... What number was it...?
Number nine!
Here, stand back.
Poi!
Okay, let’s go!
Whoa, you’re a witch!
I knew it! You are a witch!
What are you talking about?
These are Hoi Poi Capsules;
they’re commonplace in the capital!
It’s not witchcraft!
Just get in behind me already!
Ready? Here we go!
Wow! This goes way faster
than me runnin’!
Hey, watch where you’re grabbing!
The mountains behind them, Gokū and Blooma
set off on their fantastic, mysterious adventure.
Whoa, that move was awesome!
We were up flyin’ in the sky!
Sure were!
Didn’t think the slope
would be that steep...
Please excuse me.
Just wait here, I’ll be back soon!
Huh? Where ya goin’?
Man, you’re dim!
When a lady says that,
she’s obviously gonna go pee!
Oh, yer just takin’ a leak?
And don’t follow me!
She coulda just gone pee
right here... Weirdo.
Whatsa matter?
Did a snake bite yer wiener?!
Who’re you?!
I’m Gokū.
D’ya know her?
Sure I do.
I need to have a little talk with her,
so why don’t you wait here?
Whuh? I’m all tied up...
Later, blockhead! Bye-bye!
It’s been so long
since I’ve had human meat!
I’m gonna savor the taste o’ you!
Hey! How long d’ya want me to wait?!
What are you doing?!
Come save me!
Dummy! Idiot! Moron!
Huh? Oh, ya want me to save you?
Ya shoulda said so sooner!
But now what?
I can’t fly...
Oh, I know!
Can I ride this?
Pretty sure she gave
this thing a twist...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yes! It’s movin’!
Good, good, good, good!
Here goes!
Darn, I can’t reach!
Gokū!
Moron!
Extend, rod!
Have a taste o’ my prized Compliant Rod!
Help me!
You got it!
There!
If she fell down there,
then I guess I didn’t save ‘er...
I went and peed anyway...
That’s good!
Gokū and Blooma’s journey has only
just begun, and look at what’s happened.
Now, what awaits them next?
oide fantajii sukisa misuterii
Come along for fantasy, for love, for mystery
kimi no wakasa kakusanai de
Don't you go hiding your youth
fushigi shitakute bouken shitakute
Wanting for mystery, wanting for adventure
dare mo minna uzu uzu shite ru
Everyone out there's raring to go
otona no furi shite akiramecha
If you act like an adult and give up
kiseki no nazo nado tokenai yo
The miraculous riddle will never be solved
motto wairudo ni
Go live even more wild
motto takumashiku ikite goran
and braver than ever
romantikku ageru yo
I'll give you romance!
honto no yuuki misete kuretara
If you show me true courage
romantikku ageru yo
I'll give you romance!
tokimeku mune ni
When that heart of yours pounds,
kira kira hikatta yume o ageru yo
I'll give you a glittering dream
Preview
Heya!
This is awesome!
There’s so much to see outside!
It’s all so surprisin’!
This is my first time meetin’ a girl!
It’s kinda secret, but didja know that
girls have their butts in a weird place?
A-And, there’re other people out there
with their eyes on the Dragon Balls!
Next time, on Dragon Ball:
“What the Heck?! No Balls!”
Watch it, won’tcha?
Next Time
What the Heck?! No Balls!